homerun.co 2019-07-17

# Homerun: Privacy Policy

We are Homerun B.V., located at Singel 542, 1017 AZ Amsterdam, The Netherlands. Trade Register number 66911524. Our VAT number is NL856750189B01. Phone: +31 20 261582. Email: [info@homerun.co](mailto:info@homerun.co). We offer recruitment software that enables our customers to create a career site and personalised job openings. 

This Privacy Statement applies to processing of personal data on our public websites including, but not limited to: www.homerun.co, www.artofwork.co, library.artofwork.co, interviews.artofwork.co, playbooks.homerun.co, updates.homerun.co, help.homerun.co, blog.homerun.co, developers.homerun.co, www.getrevue.co/profile/homerun (together the “Websites”). It is not related to processing of candidate data by our customers on their respective career sites, and it also does not relate to the use of our own career site at jobs.homerun.co. This document is intended to inform you, as a user of our Websites, about which personal data we collect, how we use this data and for which purposes we do that.

We comply with all provisions of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the European Union (EU).

If you are younger than sixteen years, you cannot use our Websites without the permission of your parents or legal guardian.

 **We collect the following personal data:**  
\- Your email address, if you provide it. When you provide your email address in order to subscribe to our newsletter, you provide consent for us to send email newsletters relating to our services.   
\- Conversations you have with our staff through the chat functionality on some of our websites. We use this assist you in the use of the website or our services. We do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests, specifically informing you about the functionality of our software and/or selling our software to you. The chat functionality is provided by Intercom, which is based in the United States of America, and adheres to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.

We will keep your personal data only for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected or processed, unless we have to keep it for legitimate business, tax or legal purposes. For newsletter subscribers, this means we store your email address until you withdraw consent by unsubscribing, which can be done at any time.

We will not share your personal data with third parties unless it is needed in order to provide the requested service to you, or when we have a legal obligation to do so. Any third parties will process your personal data in conformance with this statement.

You have the right to obtain from us: information about how we process your personal data, as well as a copy of the personal data which we have stored about you. You also have the right to correct, update, shield or delete your personal data in our records, as well as data portability of your personal data to a third party, and to report any misuse of your personal data.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about how we handle personal data or if you wish to make use of your rights described above, please contact us at privacy@homerun.co. If you have any complaints about this statement or about how we handle your personal data you can also file a complaint at the Dutch Data Protection Agency (Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens). For more information see [this page](https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/).

We may update this statement at a later stage. If we make significant changes, we will post a notification on our Websites; the new statement will be effective immediately upon posting. By continuing to access our Websites, you agree to be bound by the revised statement.

 **Cookies**  
Cookies are text files that are set by our Website(s) into the browser on your computer or mobile device. The next time you visit, those cookies allow us to recognise your device. We use cookies across our Websites mostly for analytical reasons: to analyse visitor behaviour (e.g. which pages are viewed often) in order to optimise the usability of the Websites.

We make use of the following third party tools which use cookies. We use Google Tag Manager to implement third party tools. We use the Facebook pixel, Twitter pixel, LinkedIn pixel and Google AdWords Remarketing pixel in order to measure conversion of our advertisements on social media. For general website analytics we use Google Analytics. For website usage analytics we make use of MixPanel and Hotjar. The website is translated through use of Localize, which uses functional cookies to remember the preferred language. We use YouTube and Vimeo to display product videos. The chat functionality is provided by Intercom and uses functional cookies to remember earlier conversations. Our Help Center articles are served by Zendesk.

You can use the settings within your browser to control the cookies that are set on your computer.  To learn more, please look at the cookie settings available in your specific web browser(s): [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647) \- [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) \- [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) \- [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac). You may also visit [youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/) for details on how to remove cookies of specific parties and for further information on cookies.
